You
Nice kick I told you open your body when you kill the ball
How many times do I have to break it down before you get it?
I'm getting tired of explaining to you over and over again
You've got to be the densest person I've ever met you brainless saggy-haired moron
If you were in my gang, I'd tie you to my bike and drag your sorry ass all over town
Maybe the speed bumps would give your brain the jump start indeed
What? That's messed up! You can't just threaten people, man. You don't know the first thing about teaching
Ugh, I've had enough. Why are you making me kick balls against the wall anyway?
If that's all you wanted me to do, then why are you here? Set it up at least.
Give me a moving target to hit.
Not yet. You're not even close to ready for that.
What?
The first thing on the docket is trying to fix all those bad habits of yours.
But you're not getting it. Problems your head more than anything.
What's that supposed to mean?
See, the goal's not only to kill the ball.
You also gotta think about and be ready for what comes next.
Just kick it at the wall.
Take this!
Quick, pass it straight back to me.
That was way too slow.
Killing the ball's not the end of it.
It's supposed to set you up for what comes next.
That's why it's done in the first place.
You're killing it for funsies!
Is that finally starting to get through that thick skull of your ass?
It's like I'm talking to a brick wall over here.
Why are you not getting it?
You gotta open your body, you hear me?
What do you mean, open my body?
You keep repeating the same thing, but it doesn't make any damn sense.
I guess you're right.
Kind of vague, huh?
Since explaining it to me doesn't work,
why don't you show me instead?
How's that?
I bet you can't kill a ball that's coming at you out of nowhere.
That touch was perfect.
Pure poetry in motion.
And that's not the only thing.
He kicked the ball with such precision.
That was lightning fast.
He received the ball and kicked it in the same movement.
Wait, I think I get it.
Huh?
What you did.
The way you killed the ball there.
I see.
So by open, what you mean is...
Oh, sorry.
I wasn't laughing at you or nothing, Ashito.
Yeah, you just made me remember something.
Back in fifth grade,
I went to the National Center for the first time.
The thing is, everyone there knew about me and my upbringing,
which meant that no one paid any attention to me.
In fact, it seemed like they were trying to avoid me.
So I was feeling low when I first met him.
Hey.
You got some real talent there, kid.
Oh.
And for the next 15 minutes,
this guy watched me practice and gave me advice.
He was one of the best teachers I'd ever met.
He knew the exact right way to word things
so they'd stick in my slow, stupid brain.
Thing is...
Quit being stingy, old man.
I don't have all day to waste.
Can't you just tell me what I gotta do to get better?
He had a certain style.
He'd always stop right before he got to the point
where he was spelling it out for me.
I'm not gonna hand you everything.
You're gonna have to find out the answers by yourself.
If you figure it out on your own,
you'll never forget it.
It was Fukuda,
manager of the Asperion Junior Youth Team.
That was his title back then.
Oh.
After that day,
I took the advice he gave me during that 15-minute session
and ended up filling in the blanks
of what he was trying to teach me.
Then practiced it over and over again.
The old man coached you.
Well, well.
I guess he gives good advice when he wants to.
Hey!
I had a feeling you'd be out here training.
Hate to break it to you,
but you suck at lying.
Thought you could sneak off without us, huh?
No way I'm gonna let you beat me that easily.
A couple of busybodies.
If you can figure it out on your own,
you'll never forget it.
We'll round off this week's drills
with something different.
You'll be playing a four-on-four minigame today.
But,
teams will play in a diamond formation.
In this game,
you're only allowed to dribble upfield.
Also,
you're prohibited from taking any long shots
or one-on-one challenges.
In other words,
you and your team must pass your way to the goal.
If you can't kill and kick the ball,
you won't be able to take part in this game.
In which case,
you'll have to leave the field.
You gonna be okay?
Tyra.
Just keep passing the ball to me.
There's no need to go easy.
All right, let's go.
Your body's way too stiff.
You gotta loosen up.
Nice.
Pass it back.
All I gotta do is relax.
Even though it's a minigame,
it's still a game,
which means I can have all the fun I want.
Aoi's their weakest link.
Pressure him and he'll cave in.
Press him!
You keep kicking the ball way too low.
I refuse to give up.
The goal's not only to kill the ball.
You gotta be ready for what comes next.
Here.
What I'm trying to do is move the ball.
I have to think about where I want it to go
before I even touch it.
Before I even touch it.
This entire time.
I was so hung up on making sure that I stopped the ball.
All I focused on was keeping it at my feet.
Even when I was being crowded.
Right back at you, Aoi.
But that's not how you do it.
Ah!
You gotta open your body.
You hear me?
I open my body to widen my field of view.
That way I can position myself to pass the ball anywhere.
Since I'm right-footed,
I'll kill the ball so it stops diagonally to my right.
Nagano's coming in for the tackle,
but he's still too far away.
It feels like I've got so much more time
to think and move now.
You're finally getting it, Ashito.
Huh?
Every training drill we do has a purpose.
If I understand the reasoning behind each drill
and focus on improving that aspect,
I'll get even better.
I really owe you guys Tachibana,
Otomo, and Togashi.
Here!
Nice!
Our strategy isn't working out.
Change it up.
Let's block all their passing channels.
So awesome!
Dumball.
Owie!
It never occurred to me
that something as simple as how I stopped the ball
would be so important.
By learning how to do it the right way,
it feels like the scope of my soccer
has broadened.
Get in there!
Oh, crap!
Eat that!
Oh, yeah!
Nice one, Taita!
Great shot!
And of course, nice one, May!
I'm the best!
Pass!
Yeah.
Good stuff, Ashito.
I know you've been helping
with his nighttime training sessions.
He's improved.
Crazy fast, too.
So tell me,
what all did you teach him?
Nothing much,
just the normal stuff.
I didn't teach him
about barking instructions.
That guy
has got the eyes.
Finally,
he's found his way
to the starting line.
Ashito Owie,
I will teach you
how to play soccer.
Manager Shimomura,
thanks for helping us
round out our training session.
It was a good practice game.
I should have never
agreed to this match.
This isn't how
high schoolers play soccer.
They're on a whole
different level.
The number one team
in the U18 Premier League,
the Tokyo City
Asperion Youth Club.
Manager Fukuda,
your players over there,
are they okay?
They seem more
exhausted than the others.
Yeah,
those guys just recently
joined the A-Team.
And, well,
they need a little time
to adjust.
Something doesn't seem right.
Is it really because
they're new to the team?
You look pathetic.
Get on your feet,
newbie.
Akutsu,
this is how we do
things around here.
Don't like it?
Leave.
Shape up or ship out.
It's a shame
Kuribayashi isn't here.
We could have scored
four more goals.
You better not be
blaming us for that.
Of course not.
That isn't what I meant.
What I'm saying is,
this isn't even close
to the soccer manager
Fukuda had in mind.
Can it!
All of you!
Save it for later!
Do us a favor
and quit bringing up
people who aren't here.
We're the only members
of the A-Team now.
Seriously?
We got nine goals
and they're arguing
about how we could
have scored more?
I never imagined
that the A-Team
would be this good.
The soccer that I've
known up to this point
is nothing compared
to the soccer
these guys play.
Thanks for the chow!
Oh, it's so good!
The fairy taste
of the meat bear
is perfectly
with the raw egg yolk.
It's as if they were
made to go together.
The more I chewed,
the more delicious meat
flavored breads
are on my mouth.
Just shut up and eat!
Seriously, dude.
You can't let your guard down
because you learned
how to kill the ball properly.
You better not start
slacking off.
You've still got to work
on your handling skills.
Otherwise,
you won't be able
to keep up.
Right!
I learned a whole bunch
from playing
in today's game, though.
And I'm not going to
stop my nighttime practices.
I want to keep
this momentum going.
Oh, perfect.
Just what I was looking for.
Yeah!
I thought you might
want some hot sauce.
And this, too.
Huh?
You both got
the seaweed glass noodle salad,
so I grabbed
these for you guys.
Wait a minute.
Not that I don't
appreciate it,
but why were you
watching what we ordered?
I wasn't paying
any particular attention.
I just saw it
out of the corner
of my eye.
Uh...
From here?
Oh, my...
I didn't teach him
about barking instructions.
He's improving
at an incredible rate.
How is that even possible?
Does he have something
other people don't?
Huh?
Yeah.
There's something
you should know,
Aoi, so listen up.
I heard starting tomorrow,
we're finally going to be
training regularly
with the A-team.
And according to the rumors,
most new players
can't make it
through the first day.
Gotta wonder
what they have
in store for us.
Uh, let's see.
It's nice to meet you all.
I'm the captain
of...
of A-team,
Kenta Yoshitsune.
I hope our teams
can get along
with each other,
and if you have
any questions,
feel free to ask away.
I'm more than happy
to answer.
Of course,
I was new too,
so don't feel me.
Um, excuse me,
Yoshitsune?
Uh, I didn't really
catch that.
Let's work together.
Real hard.
Super hard.
He doesn't look it,
but he was
the Premier League's
top scorer.
Huh?
As you all know,
today marks the first time
the A and B teams
will be training together.
I hope this will inspire
both teams to achieve
greater heights
and try to get along.
Oh, right.
I remember.
Kuruta said that it was
the junior youth team's
dream to be coached
by the old man.
So what if the training's
supposed to be hard?
If it wasn't,
it'd be boring.
I'll keep up with them
even if it kills me.
I think that's enough
introduction.
Let's start this off
with a game.
Though, it'll be 11 on 21.
First, let's have 11 B team
players against 21
from the A team.
What?
What the hell?
This is crazy!
What's with this game
of 11 on 21?
They won't even tell us
the reason behind it.
Huh?
The old man's laughing at us?
This isn't soccer.
Right.
Time to change it up.
This time there'll be
11 on the A team
and 21 on the B team.
Also, we'll have the B team
kick the ball off.
He's so relaxed about this.
It's like a schoolyard game.
Please tell me
this isn't the actual training.
Ashito, let's go!
We've got a numbers advantage!
We can do this!
What the...
Akitsu usually plays
center-back.
Well, I guess positions
don't matter as much
with this many players.
If we can spread them out
on the field,
we'll be able to score!
Huh?
There aren't any openings.
Wait.
Where am I supposed to go?
Take it out to the wing!
Their defense is weak there!
Let's push in!
Here!
Nice!
Even with a 10-man disadvantage,
the smaller team
can still make plays,
you know.
Especially when it's
against players like you
who don't know
the first thing about soccer.
It's a piece of cake.
Huh?
Come again?
You said it's 11 on 21?
Yeah.
Well, I would have preferred
to show you something
a bit more exciting.
Seeing as you came all the way here
to interview the players
and coaches.
Please.
This is exciting enough.
I'm sure manager Fukuda
is cooking something up.
Hey, Sekia.
Don't you think you're
a little too invested
in the Asperion Club?
Maybe.
But you'll soon see.
The Asperion Youth's A-Team.
It's actually a den of monsters.
What?
How do they keep scoring on us?
There are 21 of us
on the field.
But we still can't handle them.
It's becoming clear
just how far above us
the A-Team is
in terms of skill and fitness.
That's not even the reason
we're losing.
And it's not about
the numbers either.
Ugh, this is so messed up!
How do we play
with 21 players?
I have no idea
what each person
should be doing!
Whatever's going on here,
it's definitely not soccer!
I agree with Aoi.
We have an overwhelming
numbers advantage.
If we just played normally,
we could score.
But we haven't been,
so we'll fix that right now.
Let's play soccer.
Take a look.
Newbies are figuring out a plan.
At least they're trying to.
Taita, Nagano,
you aren't gonna help them out?
They were thinking
we'd leave it up to them.
Is that all right?
They aren't pressing up
any further.
So this is how
they're controlling the game.
It's their strategy.
Even though we have
nearly double their players
on the field,
the A-Team
has positioned themselves perfectly.
They've closed off
all avenues
we could attack from.
I think I get it.
They've managed
to turn this game
into a turf war.
Owie!
Leave it to me!
Forget about the numbers!
Just play like normal!
We can still win this!
I hear ya!
That having been said,
the A-Team
are unbelievably strong opponents.
Their skills
and physical capabilities
are way above
the high school level.
And from only
a couple minutes of play,
it's obvious
the gulf between us
is enormous.
Damn it!
They haven't even
shown off a glimpse
of what they can really do.
This entire game,
they've been toying with us!
Asuri!
Get your head in the game!
We're gonna play normally, right?
We can't do that
if you're daydreaming.
Come on!
Let's focus on the basics!
That's right.
Wait!
Bring it back, Owie!
Huh?
What the hell, dude?
I could've carried it
all the way to the goal there!
Owie!
Pay attention to our movements!
One more time!
Play normally.
If I can just stall
and hold the ball up here,
I'll be able to pass it
to Rowan or Tachibana
who are running in.
There's also an open space
behind Akutsu.
I could try to get past him.
If I did,
then I could score!
Huh?
What's going on?
Why'd that opening disappear?
Oh!
Owie!
What did you pass to me,
you idiot?
What an incredible play!
Okay, time's up.
Oh!
Huh?
Ashito.
Weren't you the one
who said to focus
on just the basics?
Huh?
You talk such a big game,
but you don't even know
what the basics are.
Isn't that right?
Huh?
I'm sure you're confused.
And right now,
you're wondering
why were Kurada and Asari
mad at you?
But of all 21 players
on your team,
why did only those two
get so upset?
I want you to find the answer
to that question.
Figuring it out
is your next assignment.
I want you to find the answer
to that question.
Figuring it out is your next assignment.
Next time on Awashi, no compromises.